http://www.deltasystemsinc.com/privacy-policy/

Switches
Power take-off Switches (PTO)
Privacy Policy
Delta Systems, Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Delta System, Inc.’s Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Delta website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Delta Systems, Inc. collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Delta also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Delta. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. Delta Systems, Inc. uses this information for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Delta’s Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Delta’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Delta Systems, Inc. does not read any of your private online communications.
Delta Systems, Inc. encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Delta so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Delta is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of Delta and Delta’s family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
Delta Systems, Inc. collects and uses your personal information to operate the Delta Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Delta also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Delta Systems, Inc. and its affiliates. Delta may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Delta Systems, Inc. does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Delta may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Delta may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Delta and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Delta Systems, Inc. does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Delta Systems, Inc. keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Delta, in order to determine what Delta services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Delta to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Delta’s Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Delta or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Delta; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Delta, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Delta Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Delta pages, or register with Delta’s site or services, a cookie helps Delta to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Delta Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the specific features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of Delta services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Delta Systems, Inc. secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Delta secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Delta Systems, Inc. will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Delta encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Delta is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Delta welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Delta has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Delta Systems, Inc. at Sales@deltasystemsinc.com.
Designed and Manufactured in the United States
Contact Us
Delta Systems Inc.1734 Frost Rd.Streetsboro, OH 44241
(330) 626-2811Email
Facebook LinkedIn YouTube
Compliances
Our Capabilities
Our Promise
ISO 9001:2015      Copyright 2020 Delta Systems, Inc.  |  All rights reserved  |  Privacy Policy
